Muhammad Owais

Web Developer & Content Writer

Building No. 5/8 - KARACHI | +92 347 2908070 | owaischaudhry@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A Programmer with an experience of over a year in Functional Programming & Web Development. Attended several Coding marathons. Arranged seminars regarding CS in different schools. Have a huge interest towards Public Speaking & Marketing. I'm fond of building and testing different web tools & applications.

EXPERIENCE

WEB3 Blogger & Public Speaker | July 2022 - Present

Technosaurus Computer Science Society IQRA University Joined Technosaurus Society, to learn & share my work on WEB3 & blockchain development

Social Media Leads Generator | April 2022 - June 2022 *GLOBEX Marketing Solutions - BPO*

Served as a CSR & Social Media Leads generator. Was able to generate multiple leads using Facebook Content Marketing.

Web Developer | June 2020 - December 2020

Sports Science Company, Sydney – Australia As a Web Developer at this organization which was a startup, I was assigned to manage the I.T Department.

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Computer Science 2022 - Present Igra University, Karachi

Intermediate in Engineering 2019 - 2021 Adamjee Govt. College, Karachi. Graduated with First Division.

SKILLS

- . Public Speaking & Communication.
- . Client Handling (Negotiation)
- . Efficient in using **Microsoft Office** (Word, Excel & PowerPoint).
- . Have learnt **HTML**, **CSS**, **Ruby**, **JS** (Little much).
- . Ecommerce Setup & Handling.
- . **Flutter** Framework

INTERESTS

Content Creation

Working at different organizations got to me so many things with programming, which increases my interest towards Content Creation. I do have a YouTube Channel Here it is: Owais Chaudhry

WEB3 & Blockchain Technology

WEB3 technology is of mere interest to me, I'm fond of learning new things in WEB3 & holding sessions & seminars regarding the technology.

CERTIFICATIONS

Marketing & SEO Masterclass - LinkedIn Learning

Introduction to become a Web Developer

Customer Service & Handling